CLAUDIA GUERRA

QUALITY ASSURANCE | ASPIRING WEB DEVELOPER

© Guadalajara

www.claudiaguerrabak.com



in claudiaguerrabak

PROFILE

A Quality Assurance Professional with 5 years of experience. I have recently completed a Web Development course, adding skills in HTML, CSS, React and more to my expertise in software testing. I am organised and methodical, with an eye for detail, logical thinking, strong communication skills, and a solid work ethic. I believe in doing things right, maintaining high standards. I'm always ready to assist my colleagues and share my knowledge to help the team succeed.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Quality Assurance Consultant

August 2022 - April 2024

Oracle I worked in the implementation of Energy&Water products such as C2M, CCS, and CC&B.

In different stages of testing, such as System Testing, Regression Testing, System Integration Testing and User Acceptance Testing. My main activities consisted of the

- Test execution, design and planning, as well as maintaining existing test cases
- Identification, documentation, and tracking of defects using Jira
- Implementation of new projects in collaboration with software development and design teams
- Creation of training materials, templates, and simulations to accelerate new employee onboarding

Software Validation Tech

January 2015 - October 2017

Intel

following:

- Manual and Automated test cases execution for Intel Graphics, focusing on display, media, and rendering components
- Identification, documentation, and tracking of defects using Jira
- Creation of comprehensive documentation for new platforms and training material on testing procedures
- Participated as point of contact for Android projects, utilising Linux environments

COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS

Web Development & Cloud Computing

Junior Achievement Americas

May 2024 - October 2024

• The topics covered during this course include Programming Foundations, Web Design, HTML, CSS, React and AWS Cloud Practitioner Certification.

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner (In progress)

Amazon

Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Certified Foundations Associate

Oracle

2024

2023

Spanish Native

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Git/GitHub
- React
- Jira
- SoapUI

SOFT SKILLS

- Attention to Detail
- Teamwork
- Communication
- Proactive
- Adaptability
- Work Ethic
- Leadership

EDUCATION

Physics

2017-2023 Universidad de Guadalajara

LANGUAGES

English C1